Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[The Tower of Whispers]
[برج الهمسات]
[Episode 18]
[الحلقة 18]
Five.
خمسة.
Yan Hui.
يان هوي.
What did you
ماذا فعلت
call me just now?
اتصل بي الآن؟
Five.
خمسة.
You're hurting me.
أنت تؤلمني.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
♪ That year, the pear blossoms were filled with laughter ♪
♪ في ذلك العام، كانت أزهار الكمثرى مليئة بالضحك ♪
This is my punishment for you.
هذا عقابي لك.
♪ A night of snowflakes falling in disarray ♪
♪ ليلة من رقاقات الثلج تتساقط في حالة من الفوضى ♪
♪ All the perfection in the world hides deep regrets ♪
♪ كل الكمال في العالم يخفي ندمًا عميقًا ♪
♪ The blood in my heart is the spell of love ♪
♪ الدم في قلبي هو تعويذة الحب ♪
Five.
خمسة.
♪ I'll never miss you again in my dream ♪
♪ لن أفتقدك مرة أخرى في حلمي ♪
Did you hear me clearly this time?
هل سمعتني بوضوح هذه المرة؟
♪ When everything turns into smoke, I hope we can stay peaceful forever ♪
♪ عندما يتحول كل شيء إلى دخان، أتمنى أن نتمكن من البقاء بسلام إلى الأبد ♪
Saintess,
قديسة،
His Majesty rejected the ointment.
رفض جلالته المرهم.
What should we do with our plan?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل بخطتنا؟
Soul-Separation Herb!
عشبة فصل الروح!
I've already turned Jun Che into a Drug Man.
لقد قمت بالفعل بتحويل جون تشي إلى تاجر مخدرات.
And this Soul-Separation Herb
وهذه العشبة لفصل الروح
is specifically used to control him.
يتم استخدامه خصيصا للسيطرة عليه.
This is our Yue State's secret technique.
هذه هي التقنية السرية لدولتنا يوي.
Son,
ابن،
just endure it a little longer.
فقط تحملها لفترة أطول قليلا.
Once I manage to control him,
بمجرد أن أتمكن من السيطرة عليه،
the destruction of Daning and its people
تدمير دانينج وشعبها
will be decided by me.
سيتم تحديد ذلك من قبلي.
His Majesty has already smelled the Soul-Separation Herb today.
لقد شم جلالته بالفعل عشبة فصل الروح اليوم.
It will certainly affect him.
سيؤثر عليه بالتأكيد.
[Chief of Catering Office] [Minister of Works]
[رئيس مكتب التموين] [وزير الأشغال]
What should we do now?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل الآن؟
Your Majesty!
جلالتك!
Please reconsider it, Your Majesty!
يرجى إعادة النظر في هذا الأمر، يا جلالة الملك!
You can't kill him, Your Majesty!
لا يمكنك قتله يا جلالتك!
Don't kill him, Your Majesty!
لا تقتله يا جلالتك!
Please reconsider it, Your Majesty!
يرجى إعادة النظر في هذا الأمر، يا جلالة الملك!
The Chief of Catering Office has served 3 emperors!
رئيس مكتب التموين خدم ثلاثة أباطرة!
Don't kill him, Your Majesty!
لا تقتله يا جلالتك!
Why can't I kill him?
لماذا لا أستطيع قتله؟
[Chief of Catering Office] [Minister of Works]
[رئيس مكتب التموين] [وزير الأشغال]
Kill him!
اقتله!
Your Majesty!
جلالتك!
Your Majesty, I am innocent!
جلالتك، أنا بريء!
Your Majesty has just ascended the throne and wants to kill old officials now.
لقد اعتلى جلالتك العرش للتو ويريد قتل المسؤولين القدامى الآن.
I'm afraid you may be remembered as a tyrant.
أخشى أن يتذكرك الناس بالطاغية.
Please reconsider it, Your Majesty!
يرجى إعادة النظر في هذا الأمر، يا جلالة الملك!
Aren't you all fond of saying that
ألا تحبون جميعًا قول ذلك؟
both punishment and rewards are the emperor's grace?
هل العقاب والمكافأة من نعمة الإمبراطور؟
What?
ماذا؟
Only rewards are considered as true grace?
هل تعتبر المكافآت فقط هي النعمة الحقيقية؟
Tyrant!
طاغية!
You have the tainted blood of the villains from the Yue Tribe.
لقد حصلت على دماء ملوثة من الأشرار من قبيلة يوي.
You don't deserve to be the ruler of Daning!
أنت لا تستحق أن تكون حاكم دانينج!
Tyrant!
طاغية!
Please reconsider it, Your Majesty!
يرجى إعادة النظر في هذا الأمر، يا جلالة الملك!
I have to kill them all!
يجب علي أن أقتلهم جميعا!
I can't let any of them stay alive!
لا أستطيع أن أسمح لأي منهم بالبقاء على قيد الحياة!
Kill them! Kill them!
اقتلوهم! اقتلوهم!
Your Grace.
صاحب السمو.
[Chief of Catering Office] [Minister of Works]
[رئيس مكتب التموين] [وزير الأشغال]
In a fit of rage, His Majesty killed over 10 old officials.
في نوبة من الغضب، قام جلالته بقتل أكثر من 10 من المسؤولين القدامى.
The Left Chief Censor denounced His Majesty's brutality
أدان رئيس الرقابة اليساري وحشية جلالته
and even crashed into a pillar to demonstrate his principles.
وحتى أنه اصطدم بعمود ليثبت مبادئه.
In my previous life,
في حياتي السابقة،
after ascending the throne,
بعد اعتلائه العرش،
Jun Che killed Daning's court officials.
جون تشي قتل مسؤولي محكمة دانينغ.
Because of that, he was accused of brutality.
وبسبب ذلك اتهم بالوحشية.
What a muddle-headed ruler!
يا له من حاكم مرتبك!
What a tyrant!
يا له من طاغية!
Five.
خمسة.
Yingying.
ينغ ينغ.
You're here.
أنت هنا.
They said you were a tyrant.
قالوا أنك طاغية.
Are you here to blame me too?
هل أنت هنا لتلومني أيضًا؟
No.
لا.
But I...
ولكن انا...
But I killed a senior official who had served 3 emperors.
لكنني قتلت مسؤولاً كبيراً كان يخدم ثلاثة أباطرة.
This senior official who had served 3 emperors embezzled military funds
هذا المسؤول الكبير الذي خدم ثلاثة أباطرة اختلس أموالاً عسكرية
that were enough to buy half of Daning.
والتي كانت كافية لشراء نصف دانينج.
I've killed many other people, too.
لقد قتلت العديد من الأشخاص الآخرين أيضًا.
Among these people, some of them were corrupt officials,
ومن بين هؤلاء الأشخاص كان بعضهم مسؤولين فاسدين،
while the others were traitors to our country.
بينما كان الآخرون خونة لبلدنا.
When I saw that list,
عندما رأيت تلك القائمة،
I understood.
لقد فهمت.
Five.
خمسة.
You promised me you wouldn't kill innocent people anymore.
لقد وعدتني بأنك لن تقتل الأبرياء بعد الآن.
I trust you.
أنا أثق بك.
Yingying.
ينغ ينغ.
But why didn't you explain it to those ministers?
ولكن لماذا لم تشرح ذلك لهؤلاء الوزراء؟
They were so noisy that my head was aching.
لقد كانوا صاخبين جدًا لدرجة أن رأسي كان يؤلمني.
Hug me a little longer.
عانقني لفترة أطول قليلاً.
It looks like the Soul-Separation Herb is effective.
يبدو أن عشبة فصل الروح فعالة.
However, I need to increase the dosage.
لكنني بحاجة إلى زيادة الجرعة.
[Lu's Mansion]
[قصر لو]
After the Heart-Binding Poison incident,
بعد حادثة السم الذي يربط القلب،
why is my vision becoming increasingly blurry?
لماذا أصبحت رؤيتي ضبابية بشكل متزايد؟
My Lord, the wound is in your brain.
سيدي الجرح في دماغك.
I'm afraid you will
أخشى أنك سوف تفعل
become completely blind soon.
سيصبح أعمى تماما قريبا.
My medical skills are limited, so I can't cure your eyes.
مهاراتي الطبية محدودة، لذلك لا أستطيع علاج عينيك.
[My dear parents, Please forgive me for leaving without saying goodbye.]
[والديّ العزيزين، أرجو أن تسامحوني على مغادرتي دون وداع.]
[With the imperial court's secret order, I'm afraid I'll be away for a few years.]
[مع الأمر السري للمحكمة الإمبراطورية، أخشى أن أكون بعيدًا لعدة سنوات.]
I'm sorry, My Lord.
أنا آسف يا سيدي.
[Father, Mother, don't worry about me. Take care.]
أبي، أمي، لا تقلقوا عليّ. اعتنوا بي.
However, the Yue State's secret techniques are remarkable.
ومع ذلك، فإن التقنيات السرية التي تمتلكها دولة يوي مثيرة للإعجاب.
If you can receive treatment there,
إذا كان بإمكانك تلقي العلاج هناك،
[My dear parents, Please forgive me for leaving without saying goodbye.]
[والديّ العزيزين، أرجو أن تسامحوني على مغادرتي دون وداع.]
there might still be a glimmer of hope.
ربما لا يزال هناك بصيص أمل.
[With the imperial court's secret order, I'm afraid I'll be away for a few years.]
[مع الأمر السري للمحكمة الإمبراطورية، أخشى أن أكون بعيدًا لعدة سنوات.]
[Father, Mother, don't worry about me. Take care.]
أبي، أمي، لا تقلقوا عليّ. اعتنوا بي.
If you had stayed by my side obediently, you would have recovered by now.
لو بقيت بجانبي مطيعا، لكنت قد تعافيت الآن.
But look at you now.
ولكن انظر إليك الآن.
You've really made yourself become blind.
لقد جعلت نفسك أعمى حقا.
This time, it'll be hard to cure your eyes.
هذه المرة، سيكون من الصعب علاج عينيك.
Who's there?
من هناك؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
You'd rather die than let me save you.
تفضل أن تموت من أن تسمح لي بإنقاذك.
I can't let you know who I am.
لا أستطيع أن أخبرك من أنا.
I'm a female doctor.
أنا طبيبة.
I can cure your disease.
أستطيع علاج مرضك.
If you can cure my eyes,
إذا كان بإمكانك علاج عيني،
I'll reward you with a large sum of money.
سأكافئك بمبلغ كبير من المال.
I don't want money.
انا لا اريد المال
Then what do you want?
ثم ماذا تريد؟
I haven't decided yet.
لم أقرر بعد
May I ask for a wish?
هل يجوز لي أن أطلب أمنية؟
No matter what you ask for,
مهما كان ما تطلبه،
I will spare no efforts to fulfill it.
ولن أدخر أي جهد لتحقيق ذلك.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
Your people have repeatedly come to invite me,
لقد جاء شعبك مرارا وتكرارا لدعوتي،
saying you're not used to this new place and your condition is worsening.
قائلا أنك غير معتاد على هذا المكان الجديد وأن حالتك تزداد سوءا.
I didn't expect you would still have energy to do this.
لم أتوقع أن لديك الطاقة الكافية للقيام بهذا.
If they hadn't said that,
لو لم يقولوا ذلك،
would you have come to see me?
هل كنت ستأتي لرؤيتي؟
My illness
مرضي
has truly become incurable.
لقد أصبح حقا غير قابل للشفاء.
I just want to simply have a meal with you.
أريد فقط أن أتناول وجبة معك.
After this meal,
بعد هذه الوجبة،
I have something important to tell you.
عندي شيء مهم أريد أن أخبرك به.
What else is there?
ماذا هناك ايضا؟
Just say it all at once.
فقط قل كل ذلك مرة واحدة.
It's about the late emperor and the Eldest Prince.
يتعلق الأمر بالإمبراطور الراحل والأمير الأكبر.
I think you'll certainly be interested.
أعتقد أنك ستكون مهتمًا بالتأكيد.
I made all these dishes.
لقد قمت بتحضير كل هذه الأطباق.
Taste them now.
تذوقهم الآن.
Do they taste the same as before?
هل طعمهم نفس ما كان من قبل؟
Do you still remember this?
هل لازلت تتذكر هذا؟
When you were 6 years old,
عندما كنت في السادسة من عمرك،
one day, you kept whining and saying that you wanted to eat meat,
في يوم من الأيام، واصلت التذمر والقول إنك تريد أن تأكل اللحوم،
so I made this steamed venison for you.
لذلك قمت بإعداد هذا اللحم المطهو ​​على البخار لك.
You were so happy eating it back then.
لقد كنت سعيدًا جدًا بتناوله في ذلك الوقت.
Yes.
نعم.
But the happiness didn't last long.
ولكن السعادة لم تدوم طويلا.
Then you put me into a medicine barrel,
ثم وضعتني في برميل الدواء،
saying that this time, the medicine
قائلا أن هذه المرة الدواء
would be more effective when I got full.
سيكون أكثر فعالية عندما أكون ممتلئًا.
Just consider that a dying person's words are kind.
فقط فكر في أن كلمات الشخص المحتضر لطيفة.
I've done all these things
لقد فعلت كل هذه الأشياء
truly for your own good.
من أجل مصلحتك حقًا.
If you don't want to eat them,
إذا كنت لا تريد أن تأكلهم،
I won't force you.
لن أجبرك.
Just consider this as sitting here
فقط اعتبر هذا كأنك تجلس هنا
with me for a while.
معي لفترة من الوقت.
Jun Che's changes in these past few days
تغييرات جون تشي في الأيام القليلة الماضية
have really been too strange.
لقد كان الأمر غريبًا جدًا حقًا.
Now that I'm thinking carefully about it,
الآن بعد أن أفكر في الأمر بعناية،
since Jun Che's mother appeared,
منذ ظهور والدة جون تشي،
everything seems to
يبدو أن كل شيء
have returned to the path of my previous life.
عدت إلى مسار حياتي السابقة.
Che.
الذي - التي.
Now in the palace,
الآن في القصر،
there are still many remaining supporters for the Eldest Prince.
لا يزال هناك العديد من المؤيدين المتبقين للأمير الأكبر.
They've all hurt you before.
لقد أذواك جميعًا من قبل.
Do you still remember that?
هل لازلت تتذكر ذلك؟
Look.
ينظر.
They're laughing at you.
إنهم يضحكون عليك.
They've all bullied you
لقد قاموا جميعا بتنمرك
and insulted you before.
وأهانتك من قبل.
Have you forgotten all these things?
هل نسيت كل هذه الأشياء؟
Hurry!
عجل!
Take revenge for your own deep grudges.
انتقم من ضغائنك العميقة.
Go kill them now, Che!
إذهب وأقتلهم الآن يا تشي!
Kill them!
اقتلوهم!